University of Connecticut 1998.0186
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: Correspondence, 1962-1972
  - 1969-1970
    - Hewes, Robert E. (Dean of Students) (Box 126:, Folder 1890)
    - Home Economics, School of (Box 126:, Folder 1891)
    - Honors Program (Box 126:, Folder 1892)
    - I (Box 126:, Folder 1893)
    - Inaugurations (Box 126:, Folder 1894-1895)
    - Inner City Program (Box 126:, Folder 1896)
    - Inquiries (Box 126:, Folder 1897)
    - Institute of
      - International Education (Box 126:, Folder 1898)
      - International and Intercultural Studies (Box 126:, Folder 1899)
      - Living (Box 126:, Folder 1900)
      - Marine Biology ( John S. Rankin) (Box 127:, Folder 1901)
      - Marine Science ( Peter Dehlinger) (Box 127:, Folder 1902)
      - Materials Science ( Leonid V. Azaroff) (Box 127:, Folder 1903)
      - Nutrition and Food Science (Box 127:, Folder 1904)
      - Public Service (Box 127:, Folder 1905)
      - Urban Research ( Karl Bosworth) (Box 127:, Folder 1906)
      - Water Resources (Box 127:, Folder 1907)
    - Invoices—Discretionary Fund (Box 127:, Folder 1908)
    - J (Box 127:, Folder 1909)
    - Joint Projects Office (Box 127:, Folder 1910)
    - Jones, Betty J. (Trustee) (Box 127:, Folder 1911)
    - K (Box 127:, Folder 1912)
    - Kammer, Harry (Box 127:, Folder 1913)
    - K-O Proposal (Box 127:, Folder 1914)
    - Kellogg, Francis Osborne—Fund (Box 127:, Folder 1915)
    - Kersting, E. J. (Dean, College of Agriculture) (Box 127:, Folder 1916)
    - L (Box 127:, Folder 1917)
    - Labor Education Center (Box 127:, Folder 1918)
    - Land-Grant (Box 127:, Folder 1919-1920)
    - Law School (Box 127:, Folder 1921)
    - Law School (Box 128:, Folder 1922)
    - Legislation—Federal (Box 128:, Folder 1923)
    - Legislation—State (Box 128:, Folder 1924)
    - Library ( John McDonald) (Box 128:, Folder 1925)
    - Loeb Awards (Box 128:, Folder 1926)
    - M (Box 128:, Folder 1927)
    - Manning, John (Box 128:, Folder 1928)
    - Marcus, Walter (Box 128:, Folder 1929)
    - Massachusetts Audubon Society (Box 128:, Folder 1930)
    - Maxcy, Ellis (Trustee) (Box 128:, Folder 1931)
    - McCullough, Don (Box 128:, Folder 1932)
    - McMahon, Brien—Lectures (Box 128:, Folder 1933)
    - Memberships, 1969-70 (Box 128:, Folder 1934)
    - METANOIA (Box 128:, Folder 1935)
    - Military Day (Box 128:, Folder 1936)
    - Military Department (Box 128:, Folder 1937)
    - Moratorium—, 1969 October 15 (Box 128:, Folder 1938)
    - Moreland, W. S. (Box 128:, Folder 1939)
    - Museum of Art (Box 128:, Folder 1940)
    - Mystic Seaport (Box 128:, Folder 1941)
    - N (Box 128:, Folder 1942)
    - National Advisory Council on Health Research Facilities (Box 129:, Folder 1943-1944)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 129:, Folder 1945)
    - Newcomer's Tea (Box 129:, Folder 1946)
    - New England Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (Box 129:, Folder 1947)
    - New England Research Applications Center (Box 129:, Folder 1948)
    - New Positions (Box 129:, Folder 1949)
    - News Releases (Box 129:, Folder 1950)
    - Nielsen, Carl (Trustee) (Box 129:, Folder 1951)
    - Noah Webster Foundation (Box 129:, Folder 1952-1953)
    - Norris, Robert—Continuing Education (Box 130:, Folder 1954)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 130:, Folder 1955)
    - O (Box 130:, Folder 1956)
    - Organization of Afro-American Students (Box 130:, Folder 1957)
    - Oral History Project (Box 130:, Folder 1958)
    - Old Sturbridge Village (Box 130:, Folder 1960)
    - Ombudsman (Box 130:, Folder 1961)
    - P (Box 130:, Folder 1962)
    - Parietal Policy (Box 130:, Folder 1963)
    - Peace Corps (Box 130:, Folder 1964)
    - Pharmacy, School of (Box 130:, Folder 1965)
    - Political Data Center (Box 130:, Folder 1966)
    - Pictures (Box 130:, Folder 1967)
    - Powers, John (Placement) (Box 130:, Folder 1968)
    - President's Convocation (Box 130:, Folder 1969)
    - President's Easter Egg Hunt (Box 130:, Folder 1970)
    - President's Emeritus Tea (Box 130:, Folder 1971)
    - President's Lecture Series (Box 130:, Folder 1972)
    - President's Newsletter (Box 130:, Folder 1973)
    - President's Reception & Dinner (Box 130:, Folder 1974)
    - Presidential Scholar (Box 130:, Folder 1975)
    - Project Nehemiah (Box 130:, Folder 1976)
    - Public Works (Box 130:, Folder 1977)
    - Purchase Order, limited value (Box 130:, Folder 1978)
    - Purchase Requisition (Box 130:, Folder 1979)
    - Questionnaires (Box 130:, Folder 1980)
    - R (Box 130:, Folder 1981)
    - Radio-TV Center (Box 130:, Folder 1982)
    - Rapp, John (Financial Aid) (Box 130:, Folder 1983)
    - Rathskeller (Box 130:, Folder 1984)
    - Recommendations (Box 131:, Folder 1985)
    - Registrar (Box 131:, Folder 1986)
    - Regrets (Box 131:, Folder 1987)
    - Religious Education (Box 131:, Folder 1988)
    - Requests for Literature, Catalogs, etc. (Box 131:, Folder 1989)
    - Research Council (Box 131:, Folder 1990)
    - Research Foundation (Box 131:, Folder 1991)
    - Research Grants (Box 131:, Folder 1992-1993)
    - Research Grants (Box 132:, Folder 1994)
    - Reimbursement of Expenses (Box 132:, Folder 1995)
    - Rhodes Scholarships (Box 132:, Folder 1996)
    - Ribicoff Center (Box 132:, Folder 1997)
    - Rohrbach, John (Box 132:, Folder 1998)
    - S (Box 132:, Folder 1999)
    - Sabbatic leaves (Box 132:, Folder 2000)
    - Salaries (Box 132:, Folder 2001)
    - Schechter Foundation ( Matthew B. Schechter) (Box 132:, Folder 2002)
    - Scholarships and Gifts (Box 132:, Folder 2003-2005)
    - Scholarships and Gifts (Box 133:, Folder 2006)
    - Science Talent Search (Box 133:, Folder 2007)
    - Selective Service (Box 133:, Folder 2008)
    - Seven C's (Box 133:, Folder 2009)
    - Sight Saving Chairman - Connecticut Society for the Prevention of Blindness, Inc. (Box 133:, Folder 2010)
    - Ski Slope (Box 133:, Folder 2011)
    - Skating Rink (Box 133:, Folder 2012)
    - Smith, E.O., School (Box 133:, Folder 2013)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 133:, Folder 2014)
    - Southeastern Branch (Box 133:, Folder 2015)
    - Stamford Branch (Box 133:, Folder 2016)
    - State Comptroller (Box 133:, Folder 2017)
    - State Health Department (Box 133:, Folder 2018)
    - State Labor Department (Box 133:, Folder 2019)
    - State Personnel Department (Box 133:, Folder 2020)
    - State Police Department (Box 133:, Folder 2021)
    - State Department of Transportation - George Conkling (Box 133:, Folder 2022)
    - Sterling, M. Elizabeth (Box 133:, Folder 2023)
    - Student Senate (Box 133:, Folder 2024)
    - Student Union Board of Governors (Box 133:, Folder 2025)
    - T (Box 133:, Folder 2026)
    - Tasker, Gordon W. (Trustee) (Box 133:, Folder 2027)
    - Toner, John - Athletics (Box 133:, Folder 2028)
    - Torrington Branch (Box 133:, Folder 2029)
    - U (Box 133:, Folder 2030)
    - University Band (Box 133:, Folder 2031)
    - University Foundation (Box 134:, Folder 2032)
    - University Scholars (Box 134:, Folder 2033)
    - University Security (Box 134:, Folder 2034)
    - University Senate (Box 134:, Folder 2035-2038)
    - Urban Semester (Box 134:, Folder 2039)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture (Box 134:, Folder 2040)
    - U.S. Office of Education (Box 134:, Folder 2041)
    - U.S. Health, Education and Welfare (Box 134:, Folder 2042)
    - V (Box 134:, Folder 2043)
    - Veterinary Medicine (Box 135:, Folder 2044)
    - Vlandis, John (Box 135:, Folder 2045)
    - Vouchers (Box 135:, Folder 2046)
    - W (Box 135:, Folder 2047)
    - Waller, William D., Trustee (Box 135:, Folder 2048)
    - Waterbury Branch (Box 135:, Folder 2049)
    - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education (Box 135:, Folder 2050)
    - Wilson, Kenneth (Dean, Art & Science) (Box 135:, Folder 2051)
    - Yankee Conference (Box 135:, Folder 2052-2053)
    - Z (Box 135:, Folder 2054)
  - 1970-1971
    - Academy for Education Development (Box 135:, Folder 2055)
    - Agriculture, College of (Box 135:, Folder 2056)
    - Allied Health Professions (Box 136:, Folder 2057)
    - American Alumni Council - Grossinger's, New York (Box 136:, Folder 2058)
    - American Association for Higher Education (Box 136:, Folder 2059)
    - American Association of State Colleges and Universities (Box 136:, Folder 2060)
    - American Association of University Professors (Box 136:, Folder 2061)
    - American Council of Learned Societies (Box 136:, Folder 2062)
    - Architects (Box 136:, Folder 2063)
    - Associated Student Government (Box 136:, Folder 2064)
    - Association of American Colleges (Box 136:, Folder 2065)
    - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges (Box 136:, Folder 2066)
    - Athletic Advisory Committee (Box 136:, Folder 2067)
    - Athletics ( John Toner, Director) (Box 136:, Folder 2068)
    - Attorney General (Box 136:, Folder 2069)
    - Auditorium and Little Theatre - Advisory Committee (Box 136:, Folder 2070)
    - Barlett Arborebum (Box 136:, Folder 2071)
    - Bison Associates (Box 136:, Folder 2072)
    - Board of Trustees (Box 136:, Folder 2073)
    - Budget, University (Box 137:, Folder 2074)
    - Building Names Committee (Box 137:, Folder 2075)
    - Burgdorf Health Center (Box 137:, Folder 2076)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 137:, Folder 2077)
    - C (Box 137:, Folder 2078)
    - Campus Disorders (Box 137:, Folder 2079)
    - Campus Planning and Development (Box 137:, Folder 2080)
    - Calendar Revision Survey (Box 137:, Folder 2081)
    - Capital Projects (Box 137:, Folder 2082)
    - Carnegie Foundation (Box 137:, Folder 2083)
    - CDAP (Box 137:, Folder 2084)
    - Center for Black Studies (Box 137:, Folder 2085)
    - Center for the environment and Man, Inc. (Box 137:, Folder 2086)
    - Center for Italian Studies (Box 137:, Folder 2087)
    - Center for Real Estate and Urban Economic Status (Box 137:, Folder 2088)
    - Christmas card lists -, 1970 (Box 137:, Folder 2089)
    - “Cities of the Future,” NAE-CRC Joint Committee Efforts (Box 137:, Folder 2090)
    - Commencement (Box 138:, Folder 2091)
    - Code of Student Conduct (Box 138:, Folder 2092)
    - Commission for Higher Education (Box 138:, Folder 2093)
    - Commission on Human Rights and Opportunities (Box 138:, Folder 2094)
    - Commission on University Governance (Box 138:, Folder 2095)
    - Committee on Student Conduct (Box 138:, Folder 2096)
    - Committee on Student Economics (Box 138:, Folder 2097)
    - Community Colleges (Box 138:, Folder 2098)
    - Connecticut Center for Continuing Education (Box 138:, Folder 2099)
    - Connecticut Council on Crime and Delinquency (Box 138:, Folder 2100)
    - Connecticut Daily Campus (student newspaper) (Box 138:, Folder 2101)
    - Connecticut Economic Indicators (Box 138:, Folder 2102)
    - Connecticut Educational TV (Box 138:, Folder 2103)
    - Connecticut Public Expenditures Council (Box 138:, Folder 2104)
    - Connecticut Public TV (Box 138:, Folder 2105)
    - Connecticut Regional Medical Program (Box 139:, Folder 2106)
    - Connecticut State Employees Association (Box 139:, Folder 2107)
    - Connecticut Research Commission (Box 139:, Folder 2108)
    - CONNFACTS (Box 139:, Folder 2109)
    - CONNPEP (Box 139:, Folder 2110)
    - CONNTAC (Box 139:, Folder 2111)
    - Cooperative Extension Service (Box 139:, Folder 2112)
    - Council on Human Rights and Opportunities (Box 139:, Folder 2113)
    - Council for Philosophical Studies (Box 139:, Folder 2114)
    - Council of Deans (Box 139:, Folder 2115)
    - Danforth Foundation (Box 139:, Folder 2116)
    - Defense Research (Box 139:, Folder 2117)
    - Education Commission of the States (Box 139:, Folder 2118)
    - Education, School of (Box 139:, Folder 2119)
    - Employment Authorization (Box 139:, Folder 2120)
    - Engineering, School of (Box 139:, Folder 2121)
    - Entertainers (Box 139:, Folder 2122)
    - Environmental Studies (Box 139:, Folder 2123)
    - Faculty Standards Committee (Box 140:, Folder 2124)
    - Faculty Summer Fellowships (Box 140:, Folder 2125)
    - Finance and Control, State Department of (Box 140:, Folder 2126)
    - Financial Assistance Advisory Committee (Box 140:, Folder 2127)
    - Financial Aid (Box 140:, Folder 2128)
    - Fine Arts, School of (Box 140:, Folder 2129)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 140:, Folder 2130)
    - Fraternities and Sororities (Box 140:, Folder 2131)
    - Gant, Edward V. (Box 140:, Folder 2132)
    - Gill, Joseph N. (Box 140:, Folder 2133)
    - Goodwin, Dorothy (Box 140:, Folder 2134)
    - Governors' Environmental Policy Board (Box 140:, Folder 2135)
    - Graduate School (Box 140:, Folder 2136-2137)
    - Graduate School Advisors (Box 141:, Folder 2138)
    - Graduate School Research Foundation (Box 141:, Folder 2139)
    - Graduate Student Council (Box 141:, Folder 2140)
    - Grants (Box 141:, Folder 2141)
    - Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce (Box 141:, Folder 2142)
    - H (Box 141:, Folder 2143)
    - Handicapped Students (Box 141:, Folder 2144)
    - Hartford Branch (Box 141:, Folder 2145)
    - Hartford Seminary Foundation (Box 141:, Folder 2146)
    - Hartford TTT (Training Teachers of Teachers) (Box 141:, Folder 2147)
    - Health Center (Box 141:, Folder 2148-2149)
    - Hebrew Studies (Box 142:, Folder 2150)
    - Higher Education (Box 142:, Folder 2151)
    - Home Economics, School of (Box 142:, Folder 2152)
    - Honors Fellowships (Box 142:, Folder 2153)
    - Housing and Food Services, Division of (Box 142:, Folder 2154)
    - Housing Policy Committee (Box 142:, Folder 2155)
    - Inaugurations (Box 142:, Folder 2156)
    - Institute of Cell Biology (Box 142:, Folder 2157)
    - Institute of Material Science ( Leonid V. Azaroff) (Box 142:, Folder 2158)
    - Institute of Public Service (Box 142:, Folder 2159)
    - Institute of Water Resources (Box 142:, Folder 2160)
    - Kennedy Foundation (Box 142:, Folder 2161)
    - K-O proposal (Box 142:, Folder 2162)
    - Labor Education Center (Box 142:, Folder 2163)
    - Law School (Box 143:, Folder 2164)
    - Legal Matters (Box 143:, Folder 2165)
    - Liberal Arts Sciences, College of (Box 143:, Folder 2166)
    - Library - John McDonald (Box 143:, Folder 2167)
    - Little, Arthur D., Inc. (Box 143:, Folder 2168)
    - Long-range Planning Effort (Box 143:, Folder 2169)
    - Mallory Proposal - University of Connecticut Foundation (Box 143:, Folder 2170)
    - Malone, Thomas (Dean, Graduate School) (Box 143:, Folder 2171)
    - Manning, John (Box 143:, Folder 2172)
    - Mansfield Training School (Box 143:, Folder 2173)
    - Marine Science, Institute of ( Peter Dehlinger, Director) (Box 143:, Folder 2174)
    - Memberships, 1971 (Box 143:, Folder 2175)
    - Minority group efforts (Box 143:, Folder 2176)
    - N (Box 143:, Folder 2177)
    - National Association of State Board of Education (Box 143:, Folder 2178)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 144:, Folder 2179)
    - National Scholarship Service and Fund of Negro Students (Box 144:, Folder 2180)
    - New England Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (Box 144:, Folder 2181)
    - New England Center for Continuing Education, (2 folders) (Box 144:, Folder 2182)
    - New England Council (Box 144:, Folder 2183)
    - New England Council of Latin-American Studies (Box 144:, Folder 2184)
    - New England Presidents (Box 144:, Folder 2185)
    - New England Presidents Faculty Children Exchange Program (Box 144:, Folder 2186)
    - New England Research Applications Center (Box 144:, Folder 2187)
    - Newcomer's tea (Box 144:, Folder 2188)
    - Nielson, Carl (Trustee) (Box 145:, Folder 2189)
    - Noah Webster Foundation (Box 145:, Folder 2190)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 145:, Folder 2191)
    - O (Box 145:, Folder 2192)
    - Ombudsman (Box 145:, Folder 2193)
    - Organization of Afro-American Studies (Box 145:, Folder 2194)
    - Organization of Faculty and Professional Women (Box 145:, Folder 2195)
    - Orientation Committee (Box 145:, Folder 2196)
    - Orr, William C. (Box 145:, Folder 2197)
    - P (Box 145:, Folder 2198)
    - Patricio Incident (Box 145:, Folder 2199)
    - Pay as you Earn Proposal (Box 145:, Folder 2200)
    - Pharmacy, School of (Box 145:, Folder 2201)
    - Physical Therapy, School of (Box 145:, Folder 2202)
    - Pl (Box 145:, Folder 2203)
    - Placement (Box 145:, Folder 2204)
    - Polish Studies Program (Box 145:, Folder 2205)
    - President's Convocation (Box 145:, Folder 2206)
    - President's Easter Egg Hunt (Box 145:, Folder 2207)
    - President's Emeritus Tea, 1971 May 15 (Box 145:, Folder 2208)
    - President's Newsletter (Box 145:, Folder 2209)
    - President's reception and Dinner (Box 145:, Folder 2210)
    - R (Box 145:, Folder 2211)
    - Radio-TV Center (Box 145:, Folder 2212)
    - Re (Box 145:, Folder 2213)
    - Readmissions (Box 145:, Folder 2214)
    - Receiving Report (Box 145:, Folder 2215)
    - Recreation (Box 145:, Folder 2216)
    - Red Cross (Box 145:, Folder 2217)
    - Religious Education (Box 146:, Folder 2218)
    - Research and Development (Box 146:, Folder 2219)
    - Research Grants (Box 146:, Folder 2220)
    - Ribicoff Center (Box 146:, Folder 2221)
    - Rockerfeller Foundation (Box 146:, Folder 2222)
    - Rohrbach, John (Box 146:, Folder 2223)
    - ROTC (Box 146:, Folder 2224)
    - SAND (Box 146:, Folder 2225)
    - SDS (Box 146:, Folder 2226)
    - Selective Service (Box 146:, Folder 2227)
    - Senate Curricula and Courses Committee (Box 146:, Folder 2228)
    - Senate Growth and Development Committee> (Box 146:, Folder 2229)
    - Senior Citizens (Box 146:, Folder 2230)
    - Sehffield, Frederick (Box 146:, Folder 2231)
    - Shopping Center (Box 146:, Folder 2232)
    - Smith, E. O. School (Box 146:, Folder 2233)
    - Smith, Wilbur and Associates (Box 146:, Folder 2234)
    - Social Sciences Data Center (Box 146:, Folder 2235)
    - Southeastern Branch (Box 146:, Folder 2236)
    - Stamford Branch (Box 146:, Folder 2237)
    - Stamford Branch Committee Reports (Box 147:, Folder 2238)
    - State Colleges (Box 147:, Folder 2239)
    - State Health Department (Box 147:, Folder 2240)
    - Sti (Box 147:, Folder 2241)
    - Student Personnel - Student Affairs (Box 147:, Folder 2242)
    - Student Senate (Box 147:, Folder 2243)
    - Tuition Policy (Box 147:, Folder 2244)
    - University Choir (Box 147:, Folder 2245)
    - University Foundation (Box 147:, Folder 2246)
    - University Security (Box 147:, Folder 2247)
    - University Senate (Box 147:, Folder 2248-2249)
    - Urban Semester (Box 147:, Folder 2250)
    - U.S. Health, Education and Welfare (Box 147:, Folder 2251)
    - U.S. Health, Education and Welfare (Box 148:, Folder 2252)
    - Veterans (Box 148:, Folder 2253)
    - Veterinary Medicine (Box 148:, Folder 2254)
    - Waterbury Branch (Box 148:, Folder 2255)
    - Waller, William D. (Box 148:, Folder 2256)
    - WHUS (Box 148:, Folder 2257)
    - Willimantic River Task Force (Box 148:, Folder 2258)
    - Wilson, Kenneth (Box 148:, Folder 2259)
    - Yankee Conference (Box 148:, Folder 2260)
  - 1971-1972
    - A (Box 148:, Folder 2261)
    - Academic Calendar (Box 148:, Folder 2262)
    - Accident Reports (Box 148:, Folder 2263)
    - Accounts Manual (Box 148:, Folder 2264)
    - Ad Hoc Committee to Investigate Grievances (Box 148:, Folder 2265)
    - Advisors (Box 148:, Folder 2266)
    - Advisory Committees (Box 148:, Folder 2267)
    - Afro-American Cultural Center (Box 148:, Folder 2268)
    - Agency for International Development (Box 148:, Folder 2269)
    - Agriculture, College of ( E. J. Kersting, Dean) (Box 148:, Folder 2270)
    - Alumni Association (Box 149:, Folder 2271-2272)
    - American Association of University Professors (Box 149:, Folder 2273)
    - American Alumni Council (Box 149:, Folder 2274)
    - American Council on Education (Box 149:, Folder 2275)
    - Architects (Box 149:, Folder 2276)
    - Association of American Colleges (Box 149:, Folder 2277)
    - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges (Box 149:, Folder 2278)
    - Associated Student Commissaries (Box 149:, Folder 2279)
    - Associated Student Government (Box 149:, Folder 2280)
    - Athletics ( John Toner, Director) (Box 149:, Folder 2281)
    - Auditorium and Little Theatre (Box 149:, Folder 2282)
    - B (Box 149:, Folder 2283)
    - Babbidge, Homer D. - Biographical Information (Box 150:, Folder 2284)
    - Babbidge, Home D. - Travel Reimbursements (Box 150:, Folder 2285)
    - Bailey, Clark (Assistant to the President) (Box 150:, Folder 2286)
    - Benton, William (Trustee) (Box 150:, Folder 2287)
    - Bicentennial (Box 150:, Folder 2288)
    - Biobehavioral Sciences (Box 150:, Folder 2289)
    - Biological Sciences Group (Box 150:, Folder 2290)
    - Black Personnel and Students (Box 150:, Folder 2291)
    - Board of Trustees (Box 150:, Folder 2292-2293)
    - Braitmayer Foundation (Box 150:, Folder 2294)
    - Buck, Ray (University Publication) (Box 150:, Folder 2295)
    - Budget, University (Box 150:, Folder 2296)
    - Building Names Committee (Box 150:, Folder 2297)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 150:, Folder 2298)
    - C (Box 150:, Folder 2299)
    - Campus Community Carnival (Box 150:, Folder 2300)
    - Campus Planning and Development Committee (Box 150:, Folder 2301)
    - Capitol Building Program (Box 150:, Folder 2302)
    - Carillon (Box 151:, Folder 2303)
    - Carnegie Foundation (Box 151:, Folder 2304)
    - Center for Black Studies (Box 151:, Folder 2305)
    - Center for the Environment and Man (Box 151:, Folder 2306-2308)
    - Center for Real Estate and Urban Economic Studies (Box 151:, Folder 2309)
    - Center for the Study of the Presidency (Box 151:, Folder 2310)
    - Christmas card lists (Box 151:, Folder 2311)
    - College of the Virgin Islands (Box 151:, Folder 2312)
    - College Entrance Examination Board (Box 151:, Folder 2313)
    - Commencement (Box 152:, Folder 2314)
    - Commission for Higher Education (Box 152:, Folder 2315-2316)
    - Commission on University Governance (Box 152:, Folder 2317)
    - Committee on General Scholastic Requirements (Box 152:, Folder 2318)
    - Committee on Scholastic standards (Box 152:, Folder 2319)
    - Committee on Student Conduct (Box 152:, Folder 2320)
    - Committee on Use of Humans in Research (Box 152:, Folder 2321)
    - Communications Board (Box 152:, Folder 2322)
    - Community Colleges in Connecticut (Box 152:, Folder 2323)
    - Commendations and Complaints (Box 152:, Folder 2324-2325)
    - Computer Center Advisory Committee (Box 153:, Folder 2326)
    - Congressional Letters and Responses (Box 153:, Folder 2327)
    - Connecticut Commission on the Arts (Box 153:, Folder 2328)
    - Connecticut Concilium on Educational Reform and Renewal (Box 153:, Folder 2329)
    - Connecticut Daily Campus (student newspaper) (Box 153:, Folder 2330)
    - Connecticut Educational Council (Box 153:, Folder 2331)
    - Connecticut Education TV (Box 153:, Folder 2332)
    - Connecticut Joint Council on Economic Education, Inc. (Box 153:, Folder 2333)
    - Connecticut Legislature (Box 153:, Folder 2334)
    - Connecticut Public Expenditures Council (Box 153:, Folder 2335)
    - Connecticut Public TV (Box 153:, Folder 2336)
    - Connecticut State Employees Association (Box 153:, Folder 2337)
    - Connecticut State Departments (Box 153:, Folder 2338)
    - Connecticut Training Association> (Box 153:, Folder 2339)
    - CONNFACTS (Box 153:, Folder 2340)
    - CONNTAC (Box 153:, Folder 2341)
    - CONNTEP (Box 153:, Folder 2342)
    - Controller - J. Austin (Box 153:, Folder 2343)
    - Cooperative Extension Service (Box 153:, Folder 2344)
    - Council on Human Rights and Opportunities (Box 154:, Folder 2345)
    - D (Box 154:, Folder 2346)